Finding Aid for Stellanova Osborn papers, 1907-1988
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Business and Professional Women's Club
  - Capital Club 1961-1969 World Affairs Committee (Box 24)
  - National B.P.W. 1968 Joan Roberts, Program Director (Box 24)
  - Resolutions 1961-1970 (Box 24)
  - Correspondence 1961-1969 Capital Club (Box 24)
  - By-laws, Capita1 Club (Box 24)
  - Membership and 1eadership 1960-1961, 1966-1967 Capital Club (Box 24)
  - Annual reports 1963-1966 Capital Club (Box 24)
  - Finance records 1961, 1963 (Box 24)
  - Miscellaneous publications 1963-1970 (Box 24)
  - National Convention 1964 Detroit (Box 24)
  - National Convention 1968 Minneapolis (Box 24)
  - State Convention (St. Louis) 1969 (Box 24)
  - State Convention (Washington, D.C.) 1970 (Box 24)
  - Miscellanea (Box 24)
- Sound recordings
  - Clarence Streit interview March 27, 1963, 2 audiotapes reel-to-reel tapes (Box 25)
  - Dr. Teller interview April 7, 1963, 2 audiotapes reel-to-reel tapes (Box 25)
  - Stanley Gartenhaus interview June 16, 1963, 1 audiotapes reel-to-reel tapes (Box 25)
  - Stella Brunt Osborn interviews July, 1963, 1 audiotapes reel-to-reel tapes (Box 25)
  - George V. Allen, Paul Findley, Clarence Streit address 1964, 3 audiotapes reel-to-reel tapes (Box 25)
  - Klaus Menhart interview 1966, 3 audiotapes reel-to-reel tapes (Box 25)
  - Paul Henri Spaak interview undated, 1 audiotapes reel-to-reel tapes (Box 25)
- Card files
  - Index cards, probably used in connection with her work with Atlantic Union (Box 25)
  - Index cards, probably used in connection with her work with Atlantic Union (Box 26)
    (continued)
  - Index cards, probably used in connection with her work with Atlantic Union (Box 27)
- Biographical material
  - Three houses, by Hazel F. Kompass, pp. 84-89 (Box 28)
  - Newspaper clippings and articles about Stella B. Osborn
    - 1923-1953 (Box 28)
    - 1954-1981 (Box 28)
  - Miscellaneous biographical material (Box 28)
  - Awards 1908-1980 (Box 28)
- Personal Correspondence
  - Undated 1918-July 1929, 16 folders (Box 28)
  - August 1929-December 1949, 23 folders (Box 29)
  - 1950-1978, 26 folders (Box 30)
  - 1979-1983, 4 folders (Box 31)
  - Letters to the Editor 1928-1981, 2 folders (Box 31)
  - Letters to political figures 1949-1982, 3 folders (Box 31)
- Organizations
  - Business and Professional Women's Club 1964-1978 (Box 31)
  - Peace Organizations
    - Atlantic Council 1972-1981 (Box 31)
    - Citizens for a Convention of the Western Democracies (Con-West) 1978-1980 (Box 31)
    - Fifth World Order Study Conference January 12, 1959 (Box 31)
    - International Association for Federal Union (includes Federal Union, Inc.) 1968-1980, 3 folders (Box 31)
    - International Association for a Union of Democracies 1977-1980 (Box 31)
    - International Movement for Atlantic Union
      - 1949-1966 (Box 31)
      - 1967-1980 (Box 31)
      - Atlantic Union Committee for a Federal Convention of Democracies 1949-1971 (Box 31)
    - Organizing Committee for an Organization to Promote Public Support for a Federation of Democratic Nations (Free Nation Federation Association) 1971-1972 (Box 31)
    - The European Atlantic Movement (TEAM) 1972-1979 (Box 31)
- Topical Files
  - Abraham Baldwin Agricultural College 1967-1982 (Box 31)
  - American Indian Lore (mostly Michigan Indians; including Chase S. Osborn papers) 1943-1953, 3 folders (Box 31)
  - Michigan Area Dispute (including Chase S. Osborn papers)
    - 1939-1941 (Box 31)
    - 1943 (Box 31)
    - 1944 (Box 31)
    - 1945-1949 (Box 31)
  - Possum Poke (Worth County, Georgia) 1937-1981 (Box 32)
  - Poulan, Georgia circa 1950-1959 (Box 32)
- Writings
  - Autobiography
    - "An Ozark Diary," 1922-1923 (Box 32)
    - "The Diary of an Unstable Woman," circa 1927 (Box 32)
    - "Some Other Way Than War" (Box 32)
  - Poetry
    - Printed (Box 32)
    - Manuscript, 2 folders (Box 32)
  - Prose
    - Published Articles 1954-1978 (Box 32)
    - Manuscripts
      - Undated (Box 32)
      - 1918-1958 (Box 32)
      - 1961-1981 (Box 32)
  - Miscellanea (Box 32)
- Diaries
  - Undated travel diary (Germany) (Box 33)
  - Notebook 1928 (Box 33)
  - Notebook 1930 (Box 33)
  - Yearly volumes 1972-1981 (Box 33)
- Visual material
  - Photographs
    - Portraits (Box 34)
      See also oversize folder UAm
    - Snapshots (Box 34)
    - Early Photos (Box 34)
    - Topical files
      - Atlantic Union, International Movement for, 2 folders (Box 34)
      - Awards and honors (Box 34)
      - Awards. Honorary doctorate, University of Michigan (Box 34)
      - Boy Scouts (Box 34)
      - Family (Brunt and others) (Box 34)
      - Family (Lee and Long), include tintypes and ambrotype (Box 34)
      - Federal Union (Box 34)
      - Friends and associates, 2 folders (Box 34)
      - Frost, Robert (Box 34)
      - Group photos (Box 34)
      - Historical Markers (Box 34)
      - Homes. Duck Island, Michigan, and others (Box 34)
      - Homes. Possom Poke, Georgia (Box 34)
      - Homes. Possom Poke, Georgia, Snapshots (Box 34)
      - Indians and Johnston family (Box 34)
      - Jackson Prison Remodelling (Box 34)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 34)
      - Osborn Roadside Park (Box 34)
      - Osborn Room, Bentley Library (Box 34)
      - Phi Beta Kappa luncheon (Box 34)
      - Schoolcraft, Henry Rowe ' (Box 34)
      - Speaking engagements (Box 34)
        (see also Phi Beta Kappa)
      - Travel (Box 34)
        (see also Atlantic Union)
      - University of Michigan, Class of 1922 (Box 34)
  - Videotapes
    - "A Tale of Possum Poke in Possum Lane" (Box 34)
    - Interview with Stella Osborn December 31, 1981 in which she discusses her public activities and tells how Chase Osborn brought Robert Frost to the University of Michigan in 1922, U-matic videocassette; color; ca. 20 minutes (Box 34)
  - Oil portraits
    - Portraits of Osborn by Winifred Rogers and Vincent Keesee (Object 1)
- Biographical and autobiographical material
  This series of biographical and autobiographical materials includes birth, death, citizenship certificates, passports, and extensive notes and newspaper clippings collected by Stella Osborn about her own life and the life of Chase Osborn. Notes and the first draft of Stella Osborn's "Autobiography" is included here, as well as an autobiographical account of her participation in the movement for world peace, "Touching the Stars," written in the last fifteen years of her life.
  - Certificates of citizenship, death, and marriage (Box 35)
  - Passports 1961, 1982 (Box 35)
  - Stella Osborn material, 2 folders (Box 35)
  - Chase Osborn material, 3 folders (Box 35)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 3 folders (Box 35)
  - Notes for Autobiography, 4 folders (Box 35)
  - Autobiography, first draft, MS 1943-1945 (Box 35)
  - Man from Mars, biographical about Chase Osborn, by Milton MacKaye undated (Box 35)
  - Touching the Stars, autobiographical undated (Box 35)
  - Genealogical materials, 3 folders (Box 35)
- Correspondence
  The bulk of correspondence is for 1982-1987 but some earlier correspondence is also included. The series includes personal correspondence, arranged by year, and topical files containing correspondence from Stella Osborn's mother, R. Long (1944-45), letters to and from her friend Yuki Otsuki, and correspondence concerning the life of Chase Osborn.
  - General
    - Incoming/outgoing
      - 1960-1969 (Box 35)
      - 1970-1979 (Box 35)
      - 1981-1985, 2 folders (Box 35)
    - Outgoing
      - 1980-1982 (Box 35)
      - 1983-1984 (Box 35)
      - 1986, 2 folders (Box 35)
      - 1987 (Box 35)
    - Incoming
      - 1980-1984, 4 folders (Box 35)
      - 1986 (Box 35)
  - Topical
    - Re. Robert Frost 1921-1922 (Box 36)
    - R. Long (mother of SBO) 1944-1945 (Box 36)
    - SBO re. Chase Osborn (Box 36)
    - Yuki Osawa Otsuki 1971-1987 (Box 36)
    - Hope Stoddard 1970-1971 (Box 36)
- Financial and business affairs
  The Financial and business affairs series includes land deeds and transfers dating from 1920 for both Chase Osborn and Stella Osborn, statements of earnings for Stella Osborn's trusts (1970-1985), including her trust with the University of Michigan, income tax returns (1976-1982), and documents concerning her estate, including several revisions of her will and irrevocable trust.
  - Financial correspondence (Box 36)
  - Income tax records and returns 1976-1984, 2 folders (Box 36)
  - Trusts
    - University of Michigan Trust (Box 36)
    - Wills and irrevocable trusts 1970-1985 (Box 36)
  - Guardianship and authority 1987-1988 (Box 36)
  - Life insurance (Box 36)
  - Property insurance (Box 36)
  - SBO Library, books donated (Box 36)
  - Stock certificates and correspondence 1934-1940 (Box 36)
  - Land deeds and documents 1920-1960, 7 folders (Box 36)
  - Land contract, Salmon Island 1954 (Box 36)
  - Land deeds and documents
    - 1961-1970 (Box 36)
    - 1980-1982 (Box 36)
- Peace organizations 1960-1982
  The peace organizations series consists of a small amount of material on the International Movement for Atlantic Union, the Federal Union, CONWEST-USA, and the Center for the Study of Federalism.
  - Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 36)
  - Federal Union/ IAUD, 4 folders (Box 36)
  - CONWEST-USA/Center for the Study of Federalism (Box 36)
- Manuscripts and research notes
  The Manuscripts and research notes series includes a few childhood drawings, middle-school reading lists, college notes, and manuscripts of published and unpublished prose, poetry, articles, and speeches, many of them carbon copies. One manuscript co-authored by Chase and Stella Osborn, "Great Lakes Pioneers in Medicine," is included in this series.
  - Childhood drawings 1907-1908 (Box 36)
  - Middle-school reading list 1915 (Box 36)
  - College notes undated (Box 36)
  - College notes 1928-1929 (Box 36)
  - Prose
    - Ozark Diary, partial MS 1923 (Box 36)
    - Ozark Diary, carbon typescript 1922-1923, 3 folders (Box 36)
    - Professor Fishy Speaks, "before 1915" (Box 37)
    - A Tale of Possum Poke in Possum Lane, MS undated (Box 37)
    - Three Roofs, MS undated (Box 37)
    - Great Lakes Pioneers in Medicine (CSO and SBO), carbon undated (Box 37)
    - Miscellaneous prose manuscripts undated (Box 37)
  - Poetry
    - Iron and Arbutus, MS 1943-1945 (Box 37)
    - Suwanee Silver (Jasmine Springs), MS 1943-1945 (Box 37)
    - Beside the Cabin, MS 1956 (Box 37)
    - Miscellaneous poetry, MS (Box 37)
    - Poetry, printed works 1944, 1945, 1957 (Box 37)
  - Political
    - Articles and Notes on World Affairs (Box 37)
    - Statement for Ways and Means Committee 1958 (Box 37)
    - Notes on World Affairs 1976 (Box 37)
- Chase Osborn materials
  The Chase Osborn series is comprised of non-financial documents originated by Chase Osborn, including a carbon prose travel narrative titled, "Following the Ancient Gold Trail of Hiram of Tyre and Solomon," newsprint copies of several articles on his African travels, and his series of letters, "Africa as it is Today." There are also several letters from Stella Osborn that refer to this last manuscript. Of interest are the bedside charts of Chase Osborn during his last illness in 1949 and one folder of correspondence (1936) concerning the building of the Mackinac Bridge.
  - Correspondence re. Mackinac Bridge 1936 (Box 37)
  - Following the Ancient Gold Trail of Hiram of Tyre and Solomon, MS (Box 37)
  - Africa As It is Today, MS 1913 (Box 37)
  - Articles on African Travels 1914-1915 (Box 37)
  - Bedside Charts 1949 (Box 37)
- Diaries, account books, day books
  (Includes diaries (1982-1987), three account books (1930-46, 1946-62, and 1962-87), four "scribble books" where Stella Osborn recorded her poetry (1947-51, 1952-59, and 1953-54), and thirteen daybooks, birthday date books, and travel books.)
  - Diaries, 1982-1987, 6 volumes (Box 37)
  - Account books
    - 1930-1946 (Chase Osborn) (Box 38)
    - 1946-1962 (Box 38)
    - 1962-1964 (Box 38)
  - Daybooks and Travel Journals
    - Daybook 1938 (Box 38)
    - Longfellow Birthday Date book 1938 (Box 38)
    - Christmas card list 1952-1953 (Box 38)
    - Daybook 1961 (Box 38)
    - Travel book (North America) 1964 (Box 38)
    - Travel book (France, Belgium, etc.) 1965 (Box 38)
    - Travel book (England, Germany, etc.) 1966-1967 (Box 38)
    - Daybook 1968 (Box 38)
    - Birthday book 1968 (Box 38)
    - Daybook 1969 (Box 38)
    - Daybook 1971 (Box 38)
    - Daybook, 1972-73 (Box 38)
    - Daybook, 1972-1974 (Box 38)
  - Poetry "Scribble Books"
    - 1952 (Box 38)
    - 1947-1951 (Box 38)
    - 1952-1959 (Box 38)
    - 1953-1954 (Box 38)
- Card Indices for biographical writings, 1 boxes
  These indices were collected by Stella Osborn over the years as part of her effort to document her life and times in her biographical and autobiographical writings. Included is a bibliographical file of articles concerning herself or Chase Osborn or the world peace organizations with which she was involved.
  - Bibliographical index (Box 38)
  - Biographical name index cards (Box 38)
Selective Index to Correspondents
Achilles, Theodore C. (Theodore Carter), 1905-
August 24, 1963, October 3, 1963, February 9, 1964, August 28, 1964, July 19, 1965, September 18, 1965, August 29, 1966
Adams, Paul L. (Paul Lincoln), 1908-
January 20, 1959, June 10, 1959, July 22, 1959, December 14, 1959, January 5, 1960, January 12,1960, January 21, 1960, February 9, 1960, June 13, 1960, September 1, 1960, November 25, 1960, December 28, 1960, January 25, 1961
May 9, 1961, January 9, 1962, May 14, 1962, September 25, 1962, December 4, 1962, November 4, 1963, January 9, 1964, January 6, 1964, June 6, 1968, June 4, 1968, August 31, 1970
Adenauer, Paul.
September 1, 1958, October 20, 1958, November 6, 1959, June 12, 1959, May 2, 1960, August 23, 1960, December 6, 1960, December 6, 1960
Adler, O.
September 24, 1958, October 24, 1960, February 23, 1960
Aly, Bower, 1903-
1960, March 2, 1961, April 4, 1961, May 8, 1961, April 6, 1962, May 18, 1962, June 14, 1962, July 13, 1962, August 31, 1962, September 24, 1962, September 7, 1962, January 11, 1963, February 20, 1963, February 5, 1963, March 19, 1964, June 16, 1964, May 29, 1964, October 15, 1969, October 31, 1969, December 5, 1969
Ashley, Thomas William Ludlow, 1923-
July 1, 1955
Baker, Frank C., Mrs.
March 3, 1950, May 15, 1950, August 16, 1950, September 29, 1950, May 1, 1951, July 3, 1952
Barkley, Alben William, 1877-1956
June 23, 1955
Bartlett, Lynn M. (Lynn Mahlon), 1904-1970.
April 15, 1960, January 19, 1961, February 2, 1961, March 8, 1961, August 16, 1961, August 22, 1961, October 24, 1961, December 3, 1968
Beck, Joseph, 1887-
December 22, 1961
Beeson, Lewis.
June 16, 1949, July 21, 1949, September 16, 1948, February 16, 1950, February 6, 1950, February 9, 1950, March 16, 1950, April 26, 1950, April 11, 1951, July 7, 1952, August 12, 1952, September 8, 1952, June 19, 1953, November 5, 1954, June 10, 1957, February 17, 1961, November 28, 1962
Bennett. John B. (John Bonifas), 1905-1964.
May 5, 1955
Bentley, Alvin M. (Alvin Morell), 1918-1969.
July 13, 1951, August 7, 1951
Billotte, Pierre, 1906-
April 16, 1958, May 23, 1958, June 3, 1958, October 29, 1959, November 13, 1959, January 14, 1960, November 14, 1961
Birrenbach, Kurt, 1907-
March 13, 1961, May 24, 1961, April 9, 1962, March 4, 1963, May 10, 1963
Blackwelder, Justin.
1954, 1955, 1956, 1957, September 18, 1958, September 22, 1958, August 14, 1959, August 25, 1959, August 31, 1959, September 2, 1959, February 12, 1960, September 19, 1960, September 1, 1961, October 31, 1961, August 30, 1963, June 7, 1966, July 28, 1969, August 21, 1972
Blitch, Iris, 1912-
May 20, 1955, December 29, 1961
Block, Herbert, 1909-
June 19, 1956
Bonistee1, Roscoe O. (Rosco Osmond), 1888-
June 13, 1960, May 28, 1964, May 20, 1970
Breckinbridge, John Bayne, 1913-
June 25, 1959, December 23, 1963, August 17, 1967
Brown, Clarence J., 1893-1965.
August 7, 1951
Brown, Garry Eldridge, 1923-
May 21, 1969, June 9, 1969
Brown, Prentiss Marsh, 1889-1973.
June 1, 1953. July 22, 1953, August 31, 1956, September 20, 1957, June 5, 1958, August 12, 1959, November 7, 1960
Brucker, Wilber Marion, 1894-1968.
April 22, 1966
Bumgardner, Eleanor M. (Eleanor Margaret)
October 16, 1945, December 7, 1945, July 28, 1947, August 26, 1949, May 7, 1951, April 4, 1956, July 5, 1957, November 13, 1957, October 29, 1958, January 23, 1969, April 30, 1970
Bundy, McGeorge.
April 12, 1961, May 15, 1961, September 7, 1961, September 21, 1961, October 5, 1965
Burke, Arleigh A., 1901-
March 6, 1961
Caldwell, Harmon White, 1899-
September 15, 1959
Campbell, Albert A.
January 14, 1972
Capehart, Homer E. (Homer Earl), 1897-1979.
January 3, 1959
Carlson, Frank, 1893-
January 22, 1962, September 14, 1962
Case, James Herbert, 1906-
September 12, 1962, September 4, 1962
Chamberlain, Charles Ernest, 1917-
December 31, 1963
Charlesworth, James Clyde, 1900-
April 19, 1962, May 22, 1963, March 30, 1964
Church, Frank.
August 31, 1960, February 13, 1961, February 8, 1961, July 11, 1961, May 18, 1964, April 30, 1965, April 27, 1966, November 1, 1968, June 23, 1969
Church, Michael P. (Michael Paul), 1907-
February 28, 1958, April 6, 1960, July 14, 1960, July 6, 1964, July 24, 1964, January 27, 1970, July 9, 1970, March 30, 1971, June 7, 1971, December 8, 1971
Clark, Frank Monroe, 1915-
August 15, 1960
Clay, Lucius D. (Lucius DuBignon), 1897-1978.
December 21, 1961
Cleveland, Harlan.
March 15, 1961, July 11, 1963
Clevenger, Raymond Francis, 1926-
November 17, 1961, May 4, 1966, November 2, 1966
Coleman, John Strider, 1897-1958.
January 25, 1954
Cooper, John Sherman, 1901-
June 24, 1957, June 29, 1957, July 31, 1957, August 28, 1969
Corbett, Robert J. (Robert James), 1905-1971.
August 15, 1960
Cousins, Norman.
January 10, 1964
Cunningham, Sarah Jane.
October 13, 1962, October 31, 1962, November 7, 1962
Curtis, Thomas B. (Thomas Bradford), 1911-
August 13, 1964
Dahlberg, Edwin T. (Edwin Theodore), 1892-1986.
April 10, 1958, April 19, 1958, May 7, 1958, July 10, 1958, August 22, 1959, December 11, 1959
Dennis, Don.
May 10, 1951, July 17, 1951, 1952, July 1, 1958, April 26, 1960, April 26, 1960, June 10, 1960, August 26, 1963, March 24, 1971
Dewey, Thomas E. (Thomas Edmund), 1902-1971.
March 21, 1951
Diefenbaker, John G., 1895-1979.
June 21, 1961
Dingell, John D.
June 18, 1951, August 28, 1951, October 15, 1959
Dirksen, Everett McKinley.
July 13, 1959
Dodd, Thomas J. (Thomas Joseph), 1907-1971.
May 27, 1960, July 15, 1965
Douglas, Paul Howard, 1892-
November 3, 1966
Douglas, William O. (William Orville), 1898-
March 10, 1959
Drury, Newton B., 1889-
June 14, 1945
Dulles, John Foster, 1888-1959.
August 7, 1950, September 19, 1950, August 6, 1952, June 29, 1955, September 28, 1955, December 4, 1957
Earle, Clifford.
May 5, 1960, July 21, 1960
Eddy, Gerald E. (Gerald Ernest), 1907-
January 14, 1964
Eden, Anthony, Earl of Avon, 1897-
December 14, 1966, 1967, April 3, 1969, June 13, 1969, August 25, 1970, March 12, 1971, April 20, 1971
Eisenhower, Dwight D. (Dwight David), 1890-1969.
October 19, 1951, June 30, 1949
Ellrick, Charles Burke, 1908-
June 29, 1955, August 1, 1956
Elliott, Edward C. (Edward Charles), 1874-1960.
July 1, 1946, July 2, 1946, April 13, 1951, July 20, 1953, March 25, 1959, April 6, 1959, April 9, 1959, April 13, 1960, April 13, 1960
Ellsworth, Robert.
September 12, 1969
Esch, Marvin Lionel, 1927-
February 13, 1969
Fairclough, Ellen Louks.
June 23, 1950, June 13, 1950, May 17, 1955, May 17, 1956, July 10, 1957, July 26, 1957, December 16, 1957, April 17, 1961, January 22, 1963
Fanget, Louis A.
October 4, 1954, November 16, 1954
Farnsley, Charles Roland Peaslee, 1907-
July 1, 1966
Ferguson, Charles W., (Charles Wright), 1901-1987.
June 9, 1960
Ferguson, Homer, 1889-1982.
August 23, 1959, September 21, 1949
Field, George, 1904-
August 28, 1961, September 18, 1961
Findley, Paul, 1921-
November 8, 1963, December 23, 1964, March 16, 1965, March 22, 1966, March 24, 1966, December 12, 1966, December 30, 1966, January 11, 1967, October 30, 1967, March 29, 1969, August 27, 1969, September 9, 1969, November 30, 1970
Fitzpatrick, John J., 1914
1961, March 13, 1962, June 29, 1962, September 5, 1962, November 12, 1969, April 3, 1970
Fleming, R. W. (Robben Wright), 1916-
January 2, 1968, September 10, 1968, March 17, 1969, December 18, 1969
Ford, Gerald R., 1913-
January 11, 1951, April 3, 1959, July 17, 1959, November 6, 1959, August 10, 1960, August 8, 1960, November 2, 1960, August 28, 1963, January 3, 1964, January 1, 1964, May 27, 1966, August 8, 1967, August 8, 1967, December 9, 1968, June 27, 1963, August 12, 1963, October 21, 1963, January 21, 1971
Ford, Henry, 1917-1987.
October 17, 1955
Fraser, Donald Mackay, 1924-
January 13, 1964, July 11, 1966, August 25, 1966, August 10, 1966, July 18, 1968, November 13, 1968, September 3, 1969, December 18, 1969, February 4, 1970, November 3, 1970, April 20, 1971
Fulbright, J. William (James William), 1905-
May 8, 1961
Gavin, Leon H.
August 17, 1960
George, Walter F. (Walter Franklin), 1878-1957.
July 14, 1947, September 18, 1950, June 17, 1953, June 22, 1953, July 20, 1953, December 31, 1954, May 4, 1955, July 30, 1955, September, 9, 1955, October 5, 1955, June 1, 1956, June 28, 1956, June 27, 1956, July 12, 1956, July 26, 1957
Gillette, Guy M.
June 25, 1953
Glick, Brian.
March 11, 1961, March 20, 1961, February 28, 1961, April 11, 1961, May 16, 1961
Goldwater, Barry M. (Barry Morris), 1909-
October 21, 1964
Gordon, Archibald, Sir.
September 17,1958
Gore, Albert Arnold, 1907-
October 30, 1967
Green, Theodore Francis, 1867-
August 22, 1958
Griffin, Robert P. (Robert Paul), 1923-
July 1, 1960, October 15, 1966, October 31, 1966, June 30, 1967, April 24, 1969, March 11, 1971, April 21, 1972
Griffiths, Martha Wright, 1912-
January 15, 1970, September 1, 1970
Gruenther, Alfred M ,1899-
December 10, 1954, April 6, 1955, June 1, 1955, January 10, 1956, March 12, 1956
Guest, Edgar A. (Edgar Albert), 1881-1959.
September 31, 1951
Hanes, John Wesley, 1892-
February 6, 1956, February 9, 1956, April 27, 1956
Hardy, Ralph W.
June 21, 1956
Hare, James M., 1910-
March 29, 1956, August 22, 1960, November 7, 1960, January 8, 1962, October 22, 1962, November 7, 1966, August 19, 1970
Harkness, Douglas Scott, 1903-
February 23, 1961
Harris, Frederick Brown.
December 29, 1958
Hart, Philip A. (Philip Aloysius), 1912-1976.
May 1, 1959, October 20, 1959, July 10, 1961, April 5, 1963, September 3, 1963, September 3, 1963, December 18, 1963, February 10, 1966, March 7, 1966, March 23, 1970
Hartigan, John D.
September 30, 1957, November 22, 1957
Hatcher, Harlan Henthorne, 1898-
June 26, 1958, March 16, 1962, August 8, 1967, October 25, 1967
Hatfield, Mark O. 1922-
July 10, 1963
Heard, Alexander.
July 11, 1962
Hellyer, Paul Theodore, 1923-
January 20, 1966
Herter, Christian Archibald, 1895-1966.
May 12, 1958, June 15, 1961, July 14, 1961, July 28, 1961, September 26, 1961, September 29, 1961, March 6, 1962, March 26, 1962, November 14, 1962
Hildebrandt, Herbert W.
1967, August 26, 1969, December 4, 1969
Hoffman, Clare Eugene, 1875-1967.
March 19, 1951
Holbrook, Sabra.
June 12, 1950, August 7, 1950, April 26, 1951, May 2, 1951
Hoover, J. Edgar (John Edgar), 1895-1972.
June 27, 1949, October 9, 1950, October 2, 1950, September 12, 1952, June 23, 1961
Hovde, Frederick L., 1908-
April 21, 1961
Hughes, Sarah Tilghman, 1896-
February 19,1965
Humphrey, Hubert H. (Hubert Horatio), 1911-1978.
May 21, 1951, August 4, 1955, June 21, 1957, August 6, 1957, June 30, 1959
Ickes, Harold L. (Harold LeClair), 1874-1952.
August 31, 1949, August 23, 1949
Javits, Jacob K. (Jacob Koppel), 1904-1986.
November 18, 1968
Johanneson, Alexander.
January 3, 1961, June 20, 1961, March 28, 1961, December 10, 1961, November 15, 1962
Johnson, Lady Bird, 1912-
March 22, 1965
Johnson, Lyndon B. (Lyndon Baines), 1908-1973.
February 22, 1956, July 14, 1961
Kebler, Geneva.
February 24, 1966